Contact

mertokan5020@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mert-okan (LinkedIn) mertokan.vercel.app/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Front-end Coding
GitHub
Front-End Development

Certifications

Extended Software Specialization Training - Frontend Training Program

Mert OKAN

Front-End Developer (ReactJS, JavaScript, HTML/CSS) İzmir, Turkey

Summary

Hello! I'm a Front-End Web Developer with knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, and Next.js. I have experience developing single page. My goal is to advance my skills in web development and be a part of exciting projects. Looking forward to collaborating together!

Experience

Cevher Jant Sanayi A.Ş.

6 months

Digitalisation

October 2020 - February 2021 (5 months)

İzmir, Türkiye

Arge

September 2020 - September 2020 (1 month)

İzmir, Türkiye

Education

Izmir University of Economics

Associate's degree, Computer Programming · (2019 - 2021)

Acunmedya Akademi

Enhanced Software Expertise · (October 2022 - July 2023)

Anadolu University

Licentiate degree, Management Information Systems · (September 2022)